Guide to the Yale University Corporation and University Advisory Groups Photographs
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale University Corporation and university advisory groups photographs
1901-1992
RU 751
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
4.5
(3 boxes)
The materials consist of formal individual and group photographs taken at Yale University Corporation meetings and events.
Yale Corporation
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 1-A (YRG 1-A), Minutes of meetings and administrative records of the Yale Corporation.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The records are arranged chronologically.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of formal individual and group photographs taken at Yale University Corporation meetings and events.
Photographs; Yale Corporation -- Pictorial works
- Photographs, Series I
  - Composite of portraits, 1901 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Group photos
    - [1899-1937?] (Box 1, Folder 2 - 3)
    - Charles Seymour. Robert Taft, and Dean Acheson, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1950-1956 (Box 1, Folder 5 - 8)
    - (informal photos at meeting, from an article in The Yale Undergraduate ), 1957 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 1958-1969 (Box 1, Folder 10 - 19)
    - [1970-1977?] (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 1978-1991 (Box 1, Folder 21 - 30)
    - 1992 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Retirement dinner for Ted Blair, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 32 - 33)
  - Photos of new Trustees (John Claggett Danforth, Hanna Holborn Gray, and William Henry Donaldson), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - William McC. Martin, Y 1928 and Arthur K. Watson, Y 1943, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - University council
    - 1948 (Box 1, Folder 36)
      - Oversize, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - 1952 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - 1955 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - 1959 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - [1960-1963?] (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Photo of new gold snuff box by Samuel Johnson of New York, Undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Folio, Corporation and Alumni Advisory Board, 1914 (Box DR1F1)